how did this all start why create the
song ill my father actually I think I
mentioned it when we opened I think
better be asked me what was the first
thing that came to mind when he got the
ring from my small goal alright well
first thank you to my mind was about um
making the most of your life and you
know actually it's that it was actually
a song then I was thinking of as it was
actually yes my my Catholic school
upbringing actually came into shape here
there's a song called film to the thing
so that's some of it I know why they
gave me a I entered my mind when I did
but I thought that was such a symbolic
and such an appropriate title and I
because I I that's how I basically my
life I've had to make the most of
everything and I feel like if EE D is
there to help you make the most of
everything so that's why I started with
that and from that point on it was the
it was this the big bang that started
anything so my next question for either
what was your reaction first heard of
the song I actually genuinely loved it
the first time that I heard it I mean I
think the leaves interpretation of a
relatively simple brief was ninety
percent on actually I mean you were very
generous earlier about the collaboration
when we sort of chatted about it but you
know I think Nick mentioned it insurance
companies buy from a definition are
relatively risk-averse traditional very
prudent kind of predictable
organizations and I've work for a few
and they will have songs but they're
kind of predictable traditional and all
those kind of things and we really
didn't want that we really wanted
something that not only kind of captured
the DNA of what we're trying to do as a
new type of insurance company a fresh
brand to the space but something that
really captured actually the spirit of
the consumers that we we want to protect
and I think of course the tumors all
over the world to some extent are our
consumers all over the world but the
thing is I don't have this kind of
passion and resilience of particularly
loved music and kind of no matter what
God throws of whom you just smile them
and move on and that was really what it
was that we were trying to do and I
think they've got it in one and with a
little bit
Thailand and India fabulous fun and what
also these designs that we've obviously
shared this internally as well because
WD is a variation business we have
business is now in eight countries and
weeks ago I was a regional CEO
conference took the opportunity to share
the video with with the rest of the guns
and they loved it as well and I did i'm
pretty sure that you'll be hearing this
actually in our other FWD entities
because i think everybody felt it just
really get capture what we are as a
company and so the consumers that we
want to tackle this be translated to
other languages no never say no stranger
things a little more challenging income
in languages like vietnamese yes but but
who knows but i think that i mean music
is a universal language right and more
often than not english is the language
of science or occasionally widely
understood and appreciated across the
across the country thank you thank you
Peter sister Rita sorry sister Cynthia
and sister Marlene piano but what was
your reaction when you first heard of
the star
I do love that I think two days ago diet
went to our place and he asked us if we
can end this gathering at first I was
hesitant because I know but I we said
yes with just a chocolate everything is
all over no we don't know what was idea
we don't even know who will be prepared
except for those names that we make
management but I asked him can I ask a
copy of the song because I love song
love cause all of us we have songs but i
am very on particularly within us in the
song if I ask you please email me the
rest of us home because I don't only
appreciate below the music melody but
the lyrics when I me on when he sent me
that yesterday so I started listening
Lee a bit ly um holy orders each so I
music it up I start that caregivers this
is the song and each the kids music the
song and you know no ready for this
so that they will not only appreciate
abuse our kids arena muesli they start
the day with a listen to music they
become more I yeah they start moving and
the attitude and the behavior will also
go with have in tow we are thankful and
we're grateful that we are part of this
on your company when they started I
think it was saying are in here and
rushman power plays and some of the pool
they went to visit us and we are very we
were very happy and we thought they were
coming to milk and we are so thankful
and we are grateful they continue and
now here we are and what you are doing
is not just a business but you aren't
actually life and with one with the song
of being this will be much more lives
and I hope they will also understand
they will realize that life is real and
must be useful not only for ourselves
and only for others are some problems
see all around so thank you so much the
next maybe you can tell us more about
the door Fiji's well into the orphanage
oh it's already 52 years old and before
it wasn't really a problem as far as
financial concern because we have a
school on unfortunately the school was
closed 20 in after which there realize
that we need more people to help because
we cannot just continue the work of the
Lord we cannot continue to serve value
unless there are people generous enough
to give back oh I know a lot of you guys
receive message from the Lord and now
you realize that for you to be able to
breathe and your life to the phone you
really have to give back and here we are
um we are giving your life to the Lord
and we aren't happy with what we are
looking at this guy's this kids happy we
two are happy and I hope we will be able
to continue with this although we are
really always great to touch ours
because we need more generous people to
come and help the least glass and the
north so thank you so much for your for
opening your heart to the poor they need
you I'd like I guess invite everyone
she's a few trillion to pay like p.m.
and also to jam all stations of hyper so
to do 6pm will be live there and peace
expand world share the word that for
Arab every time as a DJ to request for
music from now and allegedly here
proceeds part of it will be given the
same orphanage so I think is the best
way for us to you share the Christmas
period water on this but peace we are
religious combination we are not
recently
that's why we are banking more on
generous people who will really share
this blessing we didn't even have
funding from other countries we are just
you know the providential God is the one
really supporting my okay so we now
who want the next part of our program
which is the 01